{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732562627","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732562627"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 0d71198d-916f-4d2a-8ac1-61895c29c5f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_niwe_debe-ubao-niwe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" niwe"," userResponse":" niwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732571665","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732571665"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 0d71198d-916f-4d2a-8ac1-61895c29c5f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yawe_kuni-yawe-sisa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yawe"," userResponse":" yawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732578031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732578030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 0d71198d-916f-4d2a-8ac1-61895c29c5f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_yawe_kuni-yawe-sisa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732584831","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732584831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 0d71198d-916f-4d2a-8ac1-61895c29c5f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_yawe_kuni-yawe-sisa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732599993","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732599993"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 19f289b7-6df4-4be8-9ff3-5517b04728da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiwe_kiwe-nchi-huyu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiwe"," userResponse":" kiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732608461","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732608460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 19f289b7-6df4-4be8-9ff3-5517b04728da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuwe_hapo-tuwe-lele"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuwe"," userResponse":" tuwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732617603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732617603"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 19f289b7-6df4-4be8-9ff3-5517b04728da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yawe_kuni-yawe-sisa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yawe"," userResponse":" yawe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732627595","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732627595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 19f289b7-6df4-4be8-9ff3-5517b04728da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_waua-bali-jiwe"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jiwe"," userResponse":" jiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732639401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732639400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 19f289b7-6df4-4be8-9ff3-5517b04728da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jiwe_waje-ebei-jiwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jiwe"," userResponse":" jiwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732647492","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732647492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 19f289b7-6df4-4be8-9ff3-5517b04728da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ziwe_ziwe-eupe-kima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwe"," userResponse":" ziwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732656762","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732656762"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 19f289b7-6df4-4be8-9ff3-5517b04728da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_niwe_debe-ubao-niwe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" niwe"," userResponse":" niwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.we.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732659406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732659406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 19f289b7-6df4-4be8-9ff3-5517b04728da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.we.noShow.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_niwe_debe-ubao-niwe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732667431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732667431"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 30a4944f-0064-4336-a84e-bd8597894432"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732699798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732699796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 30a4944f-0064-4336-a84e-bd8597894432"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732702410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732702409"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 30a4944f-0064-4336-a84e-bd8597894432"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732702521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732702521"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 30a4944f-0064-4336-a84e-bd8597894432"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732735616","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732735616"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732747345","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732747345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732748906","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732748906"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732761282","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732761282"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732763380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732763380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732774902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732774902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732786699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732786699"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732788039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732788039"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732795848","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732795848"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732818701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732818701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732820330","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732820330"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732832379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732832379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732842280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732842280"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732854053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732854052"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732860054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732860054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732872306","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732872306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732878242","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732878242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732892718","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732892718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732898650","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732898650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732908307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732908307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732916635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732916635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732926096","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732926095"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732933477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732933476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.we.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732939138","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732939138"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732945782","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732945781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a03e6909-c5f4-4929-ba63-5da3faeab4d4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.we.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write___we"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732958921","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732958921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kiko_yowe-kiko-sifa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiko"," userResponse":" kiko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732968943","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732968942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngwe_mito-nchi-ngwe"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngwe"," userResponse":" ngwe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732977497","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732977496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hawa_nazo-kasa-hawa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hawa"," userResponse":" hawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549732986797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549732986797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tuna_hula-tuna-pale"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tuna"," userResponse":" tuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733003973","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733003973"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sana_sana-hema-nazo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sana"," userResponse":" sana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733014117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733014117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bali_tuzo-bali-goso"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bali"," userResponse":" bali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733026597","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733026597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuna_goso-ziwa-kuna"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuna"," userResponse":" kuna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733036016","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733036016"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tisa_koti-tisa-saba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tisa"," userResponse":" tisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733044623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733044623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hili_geni-saba-hili"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hili"," userResponse":" hili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733052615","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733052615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lima"," userResponse":" lima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.all.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733058382","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733058381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733064226","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733064226"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 38572745-0d14-4fc7-8378-4d779ec88800"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.all.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_lima_lima-tope-hiki"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733078589","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733078589"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733078902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733078901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733079511","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733079511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733088714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733088714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733090879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733090879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733091281","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733091281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733093500","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733093500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733095981","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733095981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" START_MWANGALIE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733099912","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733099911"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733102114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733102114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733102760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733102760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733103510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733103509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733106255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733106254"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733106730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733106730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733107561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733107561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733109807","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733109807"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733111393","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733111392"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733111984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733111984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733112667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733112667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733113530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733113530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733114444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733114444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733114569","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733114569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733115098","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733115096"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733117561","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733117561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733120357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733120357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" START_ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733121498","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733121498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" START_SIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733123504","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733123504"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733124655","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733124655"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733125624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733125624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733126327","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733126326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733127412","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733127412"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733128476","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733128475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733128572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733128571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" a8df685f-0087-47b5-ade5-10c4e9a29a14"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733143790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733143790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733144102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733144101"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733144708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733144708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733151621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733151621"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" START_ANAITWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733157468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733157467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733158548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733158548"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733159231","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733159231"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733162509","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733162509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733164725","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733164725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733168502","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733168501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733170698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733170698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733171338","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733171337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733172091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733172090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733175059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733175059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733175066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733175065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733176059","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733176059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733178327","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733178327"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733179900","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733179899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733180486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733180485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733181158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733181158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733182011","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733182010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733182931","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733182931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733183049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733183049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733183576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733183575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733185376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733185376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733186316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733186316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIAMKA"," userResponse":" AKIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733187293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733187293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733189221","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733189220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" START_ANAZIPANGA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733191239","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733191239"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAZIPANGA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733193089","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733193089"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733194516","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733194516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733195915","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733195914"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733196189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733196189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" START_MEZA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733198391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733198391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733198784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733198784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733199308","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733199308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733199911","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733199910"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733200414","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733200414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akiamka anazipanga simu zake tano juu ya meza."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEZA"," userResponse":" MEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733202455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733202454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733203386","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733203385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733203796","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733203796"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733203899","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733203899"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733205060","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733205060"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733205304","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733205303"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733205815","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733205815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733206072","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733206072"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733206951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733206951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733207457","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733207456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733208923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733208922"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733209669","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733209669"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733211480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733211480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733212314","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733212313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733213755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733213755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733215173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733215173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733216334","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733216333"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733217832","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733217832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733218143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733218143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733218632","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733218632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733219465","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733219465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733219769","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733219769"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733220436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733220436"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" START_FAMILIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733224875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733224875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733225709","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733225708"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya manjano ni ya kuwasiliana na watu wa familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733227890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733227889"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733228798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733228798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733229288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733229288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733229396","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733229396"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733230420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733230420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733230686","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733230686"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733231370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733231369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733232211","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733232210"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733234316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733234315"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733234724","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733234724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEUPE"," userResponse":" NYEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733235107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733235106"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733235439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733235439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733235547","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733235547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" START_KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733236885","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733236884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733239171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733239171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733240550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733240550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733241951","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733241951"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733243458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733243458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733244408","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733244408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile nyeupe ni ya kuwasiliana na wenzake kazini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733246771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733246771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" BALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733247074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733247074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733247812","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733247811"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733248102","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733248102"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733248190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733248190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733249289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733249289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733249554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733249553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733250186","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733250186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733251247","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733251246"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIO"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733251420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733251418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733252183","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733252183"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADENI"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733252668","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733252668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733256630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733256630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733258378","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733258378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733259693","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733259693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733260872","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733260872"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" MADENI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733263919","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733263918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733265443","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733265443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733271714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733271714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733273245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733273245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733275049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733275049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733276025","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733276024"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733279856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733279855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" START_WALIO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733281251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733281251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733282613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733282613"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733283301","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733283301"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733286308","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733286308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733286312","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733286312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733286316","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733286316"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733287805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733287805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIO"," userResponse":" WALIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733287808","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733287808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733291035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733291035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733292888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733292888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bali ile nyekundu ni ya kuwasiliana na wale walio na madeni yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733295288","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733295288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733295839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733295838"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733295905","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733295905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733296776","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733296776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" WARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733297189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733297189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733297273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733297273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733298263","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733298263"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733298466","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733298466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733299164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733299164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733299675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733299674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733299871","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733299871"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733300660","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733300660"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHATI"," userResponse":" DHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733303073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733303073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733305566","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733305566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733307364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733307364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733308907","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733308907"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733310908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733310908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733312743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733312742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733314283","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733314283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733317501","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733317501"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733319114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733319114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733321401","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733321400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733323361","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733323361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733324980","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733324980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733326864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733326863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo ile ya waridi ni ya kuwasiliana na marafiki zake wa dhati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733329115","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733329114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733329209","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733329209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733330231","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733330230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733331850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733331850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITUMIA"," userResponse":" ANAITUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733333169","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733333169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWASILIANA"," userResponse":" KUWASILIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733333623","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733333623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733334073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733334073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733335233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733335232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOHITAJI"," userResponse":" WANAOHITAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733335918","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733335918"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733336493","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733336493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733338293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733338293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733340149","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733340148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733352473","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733352473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733356835","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733356834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733357049","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733357049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733362145","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733362145"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" df2abfc4-fbc9-43af-a973-8880e5b69526"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ile ya kizambarau anaitumia kuwasiliana na watu wanaohitaji msaada wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733362211","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733362211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" e9484705-a844-4867-bad5-ff6e64843787"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733366839","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733366839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" e9484705-a844-4867-bad5-ff6e64843787"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733371182","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733371182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" e9484705-a844-4867-bad5-ff6e64843787"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733378775","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733378775"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" e9484705-a844-4867-bad5-ff6e64843787"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733383870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733383869"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" e9484705-a844-4867-bad5-ff6e64843787"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 0"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733396298","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733396298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mboga_mboga-maji-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mboga"," userResponse":" mboga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733404746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733404746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maziwa_maziwa-nyanya-chai"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maziwa"," userResponse":" maziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733411909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733411908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chai_chai-nyama-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chai"," userResponse":" chai"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733435051","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733435051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vitumbua_mboga-vitumbua-viazi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vitumbua"," userResponse":" vitumbua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733444110","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733444110"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyama_wali-mboga-nyama"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyama"," userResponse":" nyama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733503464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733503464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chakula_maji-chakula-karoti"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chakula"," userResponse":" karoti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733511157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733511157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chakula_maji-chakula-karoti"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chakula"," userResponse":" chakula"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733562064","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733562064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maharage_maharage-chapati-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maharage"," userResponse":" chapati"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733570092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733570092"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_maharage_maharage-chapati-ndizi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maharage"," userResponse":" maharage"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733575557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733575557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nyanya_maji-nyanya-ugali"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyanya"," userResponse":" nyanya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733581829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733581829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chapati_chapati-maharage-chai"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chapati"," userResponse":" chapati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733587671","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733587670"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mandazi_mandazi-maziwa-ugali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mandazi"," userResponse":" mandazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733593442","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733593442"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4289026f-9341-463b-89fb-269b4336fbb6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.food.lc.rand.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mandazi_mandazi-maziwa-ugali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733602587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733602586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733602817","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733602816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733603789","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733603788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733605074","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733605073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733608109","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733608109"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733608975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733608974"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733609295","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733609295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733610530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733610529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733614061","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733614061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733615044","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733615044"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733615297","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733615297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733616243","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733616242"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733619090","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733619090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733620124","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733620124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733620598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733620597"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733625144","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733625141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733625255","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733625255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" ce6260fd-f418-455a-9fca-13ccdf752a15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733645720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733645720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_chapati_ugali_mboga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733652380","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733652380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nyanya_maziwa_karoti"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733659031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733659031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_samaki_maziwa_chai"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733665684","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733665684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_vitumbua_wali_karoti"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733672353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733672353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_samaki_mboga_chakula"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733679033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733679033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ugali_mandazi_maharage"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733685720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733685720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nyama_chakula_chapati"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733692420","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733692420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_karoti_mboga_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733699913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733699913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_karoti_mboga_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733710529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733710529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_karoti_mboga_vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733717190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733717190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maziwa_nyama_nyanya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733724733","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733724730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_maziwa_nyama_nyanya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.food.noShow.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733733631","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733733630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 92eeba9c-2a32-4293-91c1-042dd6ce8243"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_comm.wrd.food.noShow.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_maziwa_nyama_nyanya"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733740738","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733740738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" bcd4576b-9748-4fb6-86ee-a7bb72f4d10c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733741884","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733741884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" bcd4576b-9748-4fb6-86ee-a7bb72f4d10c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733741969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733741969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" bcd4576b-9748-4fb6-86ee-a7bb72f4d10c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733752859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733752859"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733753901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733753901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733757781","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733757781"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733758835","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733758835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733763094","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733763093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733764129","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733764129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733768454","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733768454"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733769518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733769518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733773916","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733773915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733774958","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733774958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733779244","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733779244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733780293","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733780293"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733784374","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733784374"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733785410","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733785410"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733789875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733789875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733790913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733790913"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733795932","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733795932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733796965","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733796965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maziwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733800902","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733800902"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733801945","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733801945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733805946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733805946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" START_MAHARAGE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733808162","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733808162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733809229","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733809229"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maharage"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHARAGE"," userResponse":" MAHARAGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733815432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733815432"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733816472","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733816471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mandazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANDAZI"," userResponse":" MANDAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733820667","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733820667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733821713","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733821713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733827171","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733827171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733828212","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733828212"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733833170","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733833170"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733834222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733834222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733837176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733837176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733838235","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733838235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733838453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733838452"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733838564","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733838564"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733846877","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733846877"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" b9064fac-2b1c-4967-b5c8-8d348a2640cf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-food.rand.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733868773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733868773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maharage_maji-chungwa-mchicha-maharage"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maharage"," userResponse":" maharage"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733877297","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733877289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" tikitiki maji_nanasi-tikitiki maji-chapati-nyanya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tikitiki maji"," userResponse":" nyanya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733880326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733880326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" tikitiki maji_nanasi-tikitiki maji-chapati-nyanya"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tikitiki maji"," userResponse":" tikitiki maji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733887058","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733887058"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" mchicha_mchicha-mahindi-wali-parachichi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mchicha"," userResponse":" mchicha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733892745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733892744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" yai_yai-mboga-chapati-wali"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yai"," userResponse":" yai"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733900518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733900518"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" muhogo_embe-asali-muhogo-nazi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" muhogo"," userResponse":" muhogo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733907370","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733907370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" embe_limau-embe-pera-mchicha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" embe"," userResponse":" embe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733918063","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733918063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maziwa_nyama-kitunguu-maziwa-limau"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maziwa"," userResponse":" maziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733924946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733924946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" samaki_maharage-samaki-nyanya-yai"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" samaki"," userResponse":" samaki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733932061","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733932061"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" kitunguu_maharage-pilipili-wali-kitunguu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kitunguu"," userResponse":" kitunguu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733937537","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733937537"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" food_1"," problemName":" maharage_boga-nanasi-muhogo-maharage"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" maharage"," userResponse":" maharage"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:food","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733939540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733939539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" maharage_boga-nanasi-muhogo-maharage"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733946341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733946341"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" maharage_boga-nanasi-muhogo-maharage"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733954031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733954030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 1ed866cf-fddb-43f8-ac7f-97186e080c59"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_food"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" maharage_boga-nanasi-muhogo-maharage"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733967002","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733967002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733972181","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733972181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733973768","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733973767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733977760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733977759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733979364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733979363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733983091","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733983091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733984047","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733984047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549733984691","data":{"timestamp":" 1549733984690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734013510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734013509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734013700","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734013700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734018548","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734018547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 4d48b5b4-77c2-47c6-b093-80758ec651b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-animals.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734030204","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734030204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_songura-fisi-punda"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734035635","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734035634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_songura-mbuni-paka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734042731","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734042731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_songura-mbuni-paka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734048393","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734048393"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twiga_punda-twiga-panya"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twiga"," userResponse":" twiga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734053385","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734053385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kondoo_kondoo-panya-farasi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kondoo"," userResponse":" kondoo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734058259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734058259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_mbuni-bata-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734063082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734063082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-tembo"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734067904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734067904"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_panya-paka-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734075458","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734075458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_panya-paka-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734080475","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734080475"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_bata-chura-punda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chura"," userResponse":" chura"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734085206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734085206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_paka_paka-kondoo-ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" paka"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734090027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734090027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_chura-mbwa-tembo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbwa"," userResponse":" mbwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734095829","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734095828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" d7a1d1be-3542-432b-a0c3-3444251fba0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_chura-mbwa-tembo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734110429","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734110429"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbuni_songura-mbuni-paka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuni"," userResponse":" mbuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734121015","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734121015"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fisi_songura-fisi-punda"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fisi"," userResponse":" fisi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734136798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734136798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kondoo_kondoo-panya-farasi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kondoo"," userResponse":" kondoo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734149598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734149598"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuku_ng'ombe-kuku-tembo"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuku"," userResponse":" kuku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734154895","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734154894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twiga_punda-twiga-panya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twiga"," userResponse":" twiga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734160953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734160953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_panya-paka-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734167777","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734167777"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_panya_panya-paka-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" panya"," userResponse":" panya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734173315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734173314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_paka_paka-kondoo-ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" paka"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734187079","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734187078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_chura_bata-chura-punda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" chura"," userResponse":" chura"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734192699","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734192698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbwa_chura-mbwa-tembo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbwa"," userResponse":" mbwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734197687","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734197687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_mbuni-bata-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bata"," userResponse":" bata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734203484","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734203483"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_mbuni-bata-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549734216997","data":{"timestamp":" 1549734216997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190209_201546"," gameId":" 8c77e257-9ec2-407e-a036-ff8eac632b02"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.animals.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_bata_mbuni-bata-nyoka"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}